did you ask or Russia is the legal successor of the USSR
ты спросил или Россия правопреемник СССР
I say no Russia is the legal successor of the RSFSR
Я говорю нет Россия правопреемник РСФСР
Ukraine the Ussr Belarus the legal successor of the
Украина усср Белоруссия правопреемник
BSSR
БССР
Yeah You have
Угу У тебя есть
a chance if you ask I say from me
шанс если ты спросишь Я говорю у меня
if someone asks permission to a
если кто-то спрашивает разрешение на
question I never allow it,
вопрос я не разрешаю никогда вот тебя
what’s your name I’ll try and Denis  Denis
как зовут о постараюсь ме А Денис Денис
me Andrey, what city are you from? Peter I’m
меня Андрей ты из какого города Питер Я
from Khmelnitsk
из Хмельницка
Okay, so the question was What was
О'кей значит вопрос В чём заключался
the Stop And what to ask without permission You
Стоп А что без разрешения спроси а
can’t You can’t You couldn’t learn it the third
Нельзя Нельзя Нельзя научился с третьего
time I’m just too polite Which means
раза я просто вежливый слишком А значит
Russia is the legal successor of the Soviet
Россия - это правопреемник Советского
Union or can continue it  no
Союза или может продолжать или его нет
no why and why in order to
нет а почему а почему для того чтобы
look in order for one entity to be the
смотри для того чтобы один субъект был
legal successor of another so there must be
правопреемником другого так должен быть
some kind of legal act, for example it
какой-то юридический акт она например
must declare itself the
должна провозгласить себя
legal successor of the Soviet Union
правопреемником Советского Союза
so No show by what act Russia
так Нет покажи каким актом Россия
declared itself moreover in
провозгласила себя больше того в
Belovezhskaya Pushcha when Yeltsin was signed
беловежской пуще когда подписали Ельцин
Shushkevich and this one
Шушкевич и этот
and how
и как
he kvk kvk kvk then was Yes, they
он квк квк квк тог был Да они
stated that the Soviet Union
констатировать что Советский Союз
Ceased its existence as a
Прекратил сво существование как
geopolitical
геополитическая
entity Well, it was like that, I can tell you now
сущность Ну было такое вот я тебе сейчас
Well, article in the Constitution 67.1
могу Ну вот статья в Конституции 67.1
is how to evaluate it again,
это как её расценивать ещё раз ещё раз
look again
смотри
at the Soviet Union  did not proclaim
ээ ни Советский Союз не провозглашал
itself a successor or heir to the
себя продолжателем либо наследником
Russian Empire. Yes, neither the
Российской империи Да ни Россия
modern Russia of the RSFSR proclaimed itself a
современная РСФСР ни провозглашала себя
successor or successor to either the
ни продолжателем И правопреемником ни
Russian Empire or the Soviet Union.
Российской империи ни Советского Союза
Show me at least one act that was adopted by the
Покажи мне хоть один акт который принял
parliament there or the President there, at least
там парламент или там Президент хоть
some where they recognized themselves as
какой-то где они себя признали
the legal successor Well, no.  and in the 6th
правопреемником Ну нет так а в 6 се
article this is once again this is not an act
статье это ещё раз ещё раз это не акт
it’s like another one more time tell me yes
это типа дру ещ раз скажи мне да
some kind of act that’s
какой-то акт
where Russia is when that’s when when
вот где Россия когда вот когда когда
Russia declared independence it
Россия провозгласила независимость она
declared itself the legal successor of the
провозгласила себя правопреемником
Soviet Union netna didn’t proclaim
Советского Союза нетна не провозглашала
Independently and Pose the day before yesterday that
Независимо и Поза позавчера что
they celebrated  it was there sovereignty
праздновали это там был суверенитет
sovereignty And what is sovereignty Well,
суверенитет А что такое суверенитет Ну
this is something else Almost the same thing So
это другое щё Почти то же самое Так вот
look And you and you are right and so uh you
смотри И вы и вы ж прав так вот ээ у вас
have Russia is uh the legal successor of
у вас Россия - это ээ правопреемник
the RSFSR of the Russian Soviet Federative
РСФСР российско Советской Федеративной
Socialist Republic so
Социалистической Республики так как же
how is Ukraine the legal successor  ursr of the
как Украина правопреемник урср
Ukrainian Radian Soviet
украинской радянской Советской
Socialist Republic but not the
Социалистической Республики но не
Soviet Union,
Советского Союза
that is, Russia yes Russia is the
то есть Россия да Россия есть
successor of the RSFSR
продолжатель РСФСР
in Russia after the collapse of the Union, it was not
в России после после развала Союза
these bodies of the Soviet Union that continued to operate, but the
продолжили действовать не эти не органы
bodies of the RSFSR,
Советского Союза а органы РСФСР
a parade of sovereignties, you know what,
парад суверенитетов знаете что тако
of course I know, and then Ukraine
Конечно знаю ну а потом Украина
declared independence, why then
провозгласила независимость зачем тогда
if so, look again, I'm the one you
если так смотри ещё раз я те гово ты
asked or Russia is the legal successor of the USSR I'm
спросил или Россия правопреемник СССР Я
not talking
говорю не
FSR Ukraine Ussr Belarus the
ФСР Украина усср Белоруссия
legal successor of the
правопреемник
BSSR you know such a lawyer, Doctor of
БССР знаете такого юриста доктора
Law Chernichenko, I don’t know,
юридических наук черниченко не знаю вот
he says that not first of all you know what a
он говорит что не во-первых знаете что
successor and successor are once again once
такое продолжатель и правопреемник ещ
again
раз ещ раз
look, you have to be married to some kind of act
смотри ежен быть ери ожен на какойто
Yes, there is some kind of act of proclamation And so
Да какой-то там акт провозглашения И так
on Yes, find some act where
дальше Да вот Найди какой-то акт где
Russia Yes proclaims itself the
Россия Да провозглашает себя
legal successor of the Soviet
правопреемником Советского
Union there, if I’m not mistaken, even she did
Союза там если если не ошибаюсь даже она
n’t even declare independence Well,
даже не провозглашала независимость Ну
like sovereignty, that’s still
типа суверенитет это же ещё раз ещё раз
look again Russia
смотри Россия
Yes, it
Да
received its independence from the
получила свою независимость от
Soviet Union within the framework of the
Советского Союза в рамках
RSFSR Ukraine within the framework of the Ukrainian Socialist Republic And so
РСФСР Украина в рамках урср И так
on Show it’s interesting
дальше Покажи вот интересно
let’s say no, I don’t argue Well, if it
давай нету такого не спорю Ну так если
’s not there, then everything is so wrong, we’re talking about the fact that
нету так всё так не так речь о том что
independence was not declared
не было провозглашена независимость
Look here I am  I read the Belovezhsky
Смотри вот я читаю беловежский
agreement on the creation of the Commonwealth of
соглашение о создании Содружества
Independent States, we are the Republic of
независимых государств мы республика
Belarus, the Russian Federation of the RSFSR,
Белорусь Российская Федерация РСФСР
so there is a federation
так есть федера
like the RSFSR, Ukraine as a state, the
как РСФСР Украина как государство
founders of the USSR, who signed the Union
учредители Союза ССР подписавшие Союзный
Treaty in the second year, gave the so-called
договор д второго года дали именуемые
high contracting parties,
высокими договаривающиеся сторонами
we state that the USSR as a subject of
констатируем что Союз ССР как субъект
international law and geopolitical
международного права и и геополитическая
reality ceases to exist  existence,
реальность прекращает своё существование
that
то
is, these three Republics, what is not up to
есть эти три Республики что не до
You say these three Republics Yes,
Говорите эти три Республики Да
they stated that the Soviet Union
констатировали что Советский Союз
None of them ceased to exist
Прекратил своё существование ни одна из
Yes, they did not take over the
них Да не взяла на себя
legal succession of the Soviet Union, that is, it did
правопреемственность Советского Союза то
not exist as a subject, it simply did not
есть его не стало как субъекта просто не
exist No one took over
стало Никто не перенял
it, that’s all  Well, what does Chernichenko write,
его вот и всё Ну что пишет черниченко
doctor Look, I don’t care who
доктори Смотри мне всё равно кто что
writes what Yes, if he is based on some kind of
пишет Да если он опирается на какой-то
document Sound out This document for a
документ Озвучь Этот документ на
document for which legal
документ на какой на юридический
document is wrong, he himself is a lawyer, he can
документ не так он сам юрист он может
riri
рири
can have some opinion of his own,
может иметь какое-то своё мнение что-то
tell something  Yes, he can believe that,
рассказывать да может считать что
for example, the Earth is square. So he can
например Земля квадратная Так может
believe, for example,
считать например
that people do not exist. Whatever you want. He
что людей не существует Что хочешь Он
can say Yes, but he must rely
может говорить Да но опираться он должен
on specific, if he is a lawyer, on specific
на конкретны если он юрист на конкретные
legal acts. Well, he writes a number of
юридические акты Ну что он пишет ряд
provisions of the contract.
положений договора 4 декабря де года выт
point of view,
просто неле с юридической точки зрения
the agreement is not international, it was
договор не является международным
concluded between the republics,
заключён между республиками
between the legally non-
ээ между юридически ещё не
existent SSR and the Union
существовавшими ССР и союзными
republics between the Federation and between the
республиками между Федерацией и между
Federation and its parts, since the SSR did not
Федерацией и её частями поскольку ССР не
exist, it did not yet exist, it
существовал ой ещё существовал его никак
could not be considered a state by the
нельзя было считать государством
predecessors of the members of the Federation who
предшественникам членов Федерации его
signed it, three of these fables are not
подписавших три ты эти басни не рассказ
let's look at the story like this, when the
давай так смотри когда ээ развалился
Soviet Union collapsed, so Gorbachev signed the Belovezhskaya agreements Yes, there
Советский Союз так вот беловежские
was
Да был Был
Yeltsin, yes, yes Yeltsin and Gorbachev are two
Ельцин да да Ельцин и горбачов это две
different branches, so Gorbachev and the Central Committee of the CPSU
разные ветки вот Горбачёв и ЦК КПСС -
are the Soviet Union, its governing bodies,
это Советский Союз его органы управления
and Yeltsin is the governing bodies of the RSFSR
да Ельцин - это органы управления РСФСР
when-  then at least someday the
когда-то хоть когда-нибудь органы
governing bodies of the Soviet Union transferred
управления Советского Союза передавали
their powers to Yeltsin or the
свои полномочия ельцину либо
SFS Well, I understand you want to say I don’t know,
сфс Ну я понял хотите сказать Не знаю
no, probably not, he’s still saying what
нет наверное нет он ещё что говорит
the argument is And that means in the UN Security Council the place of
аргумент А значит в ООН совбезе место
the SSR was taken by Russia Yes, look again again
ССР заняла Россия Да в смотри ещё раз
Who took this
ещё раз Кто занял
place  the Republic of China in the UN
ээ место китайской Республики в ООН
you know the
знаешь
PRC yes that is the Republic of China
КНР да то есть Китайская республика
now
сейчас
exists no so as if in this what
существует нет так как бы в этом что
is the
такое Китайская
Republic of China the Republic of China yes that the
республика Китайская республика да что
PRC was yes And where is it now
КНР было да А где она сейчас находится
renamed simply where no And where on on the
переименовали просто где нет А где на на
island of
острове
Taiwan The thing is that in  China when
Тайвань Дело в том что в Китае когда
the revolution took place Yes, Communist
прошла революция Да Коммунистическая
Communist China captured the
Коммунистический Китай захватил
mainland Yes, and the
материковую часть Да
Republic of China is Taiwan. It is
а Китайская республика вот Тайвань Он до
still called the Republic of China or
сих пор называется китайская респуб или
not the Republic of China, the Republic of China, in my opinion,
не республика Китай республика Китай
is called Whoa, uh, mainland
по-моему называется Во а ээ материковый
China is called the People's
Китай называется китайская народная
Republic of China. That is, there are now two Chinas
республика Вот то есть Китая сейчас два
and  the founder of the UN was precisely the Republic of
и основателем ООН было именно республика
China and which is in Taiwan and only in
Китай да которая на Тайване и только в
some year China simply entered the UN
каком-то году просто Китай вошёл в ООН
instead because in fact it
вместо то потому что по факту оно
occupied most of the territories. And
занимало большую часть территорий Да и
at the insistence of the USSR this does not say anything at all.
по настоянию СССР это вообще ничего не
Who entered the UN and so  further
говорит Кто там вошёл в он и так дальше
Well, what do you want to say with this argument that
Ну а что этим доводом хотите сказать что
what is your argument
что ваш аргумен
about No, how would countries recognize that the Russian Federation
о Не ну как бы страны признали что РФ
is the successor of the Soviet
является продолжателем Советского
Union Look again once again
Союза Смотрите
in he yes he accepts
продол е раз ещ раз в он да он принимает
new countries as well Yes, that is, this
и новые страны также Да вот то есть это
shows absolutely nothing He  it’s
абсолютно ничего не показывает Он это
just an
просто
organization if Russia Yes considers itself a
организация если Россия Да считает себя
legal successor or successor to an
правопреемником или продолжателем при
act because look, when it
акт потому что смотри когда она
accepts such an act, it assumes
принимает такой акт она на себя берёт
obligations then the USSR, well, they took that no
обязательства тогда сссра ну взяли что
no, look, they took obligations the
наве не нет смотри взяли обязательства
USSR took on different Republics, all the
СССР взяли разные Республики все
Republics Yes, Ukraine, look, Ukraine was, for
Республики Да Украина смотри Украина был
example, a Treaty
например Договор
on the non-proliferation of nuclear weapons Yes,
о нераспространении ядерного оружия Да
Ukraine complied with it
Украина соблюдала его
as in its own way, that is, Russia did not take
как в своём этом то есть Россия не Взяла
upon itself fully the rights and
на себя в полной мере права и
responsibilities of the USSR was not there Was back in the tenth and second
обязанности СССР не там был Был ещё в
year that the ninety-second
десто втором году что девяносто второй
ninety-second has not been for a year since the Soviet Union
девяносто второй уже с Советского Союза
no so no so
года не год как не был нет так нет так
there zhezh uh there were no decrees
там жеж ээ не были указы
Like so I can’t find it
Типа так я не могу найти
in a couple of seconds in this text Well, look for it
за за пару секунд в этом тексте Ну поищи
and while you’re looking, tell me and this is it in general
м а пока ищешь расскажи а это вообще Вот
You’re a young guy, what will it give you
ты молодой парень ну что тебе даст Если
Even if Russia Just think about it now Putin
б даже Россия Вот прикинь сейчас Путин
Yes  and the State Duma accepts that they are the
Да и Госдума принимает что они есть
legal successors of the USSR, what is this for you, what is this for,
правопреемники СССР что для тебя это для
I just heard that you are a lawyer, I
чего я просто слышал что вы юрист я
wanted your question wrong, but why do you just need to
хотел у вас вопро не так а для чего оно
find out, I myself
тебе просто узнать я ж сам меня точки
don’t have a special point of view Well, I just don’t have it, well, let’s
зрения нету особой Ну просто нету ну
look here However  now, however,
давай поищи вот Однако сейчас Однако
the inclusion of Russia in the list of states is the
включение России в перечень государств
right successor to the USSR, the agreement of
право приемников ССР соглашение от 6
July 6, 2020,
июля второго года
but raises objections for the reasons stated above,
а вызывает возражение по изложенным выше
no, look, raises an objection,
причинам нет смотри вызывает возражение
this is someone’s look,
это чьи-то смотри
uh, there are certain subjects Yes, the
ээ есть субъекты определённые Да
constitutional court, for example, yes, some kind of
конституционный суд например да какой-то
government, president Yes,
там правительство президент Да мнение
what’s the opinion  something dude Here I am, for example, a
какого-то чувака Вот я например рист
rist, I have doubts about the clause of the
гожу у меня вызывает сомнение пункт
agreement of such and such an agreement
соглашение договора такой-то такой-то
between countries, I am not a subject of this
между странами я не есть субъектом этим
understanding now
понима
And this is not something, this is an agreement of the
сечас А это не то это соглашение стран
CIS countries Well, in short, I don’t have any more
СНГ Ну ладно короче нет у меня больше
arguments. I haven’t really studied  this is a
аргументов Я особо не изучал это
legal question, another question, can you
юридический вопрос ещ какой-то вопрос ва
contact me? I think you have a question. You
ко мне може Я дума У тебя есть вопрос Ты
wanted to ask me so, what’s the use of
ж хотел ко мне так попасть на
what Putin said? Yes, everyone laughed, even
что Путин заявлял Да поржали все даже
Scholz. Well, do you think Ukraine should
шольц ну как вы считаете Украина должна
continue or maybe it’s worth taking a break,
продолжать или может стоит передышку
taking a break?  to whom Ukraine what kind of
сделать передышку кому Украине какую
respite How do you see this
передышку Как вы видите эту
respite just stop stopping
передышку просто прекратить прекратить
what to fulfill the conditions and and everything is
что выполнить условия и и всё
cool real or what if
прикольно реально или что
you didn’t laugh when you
как ты не заржал когда это
told me this 18 18
говорил мне 18 18
years old
лет
give a respite in short Kherson
передышку отдать короче Херсон
Zaporozhye region Donetsk
запорожскую область донецкую
Lugansk respite real
луганскую передышка реаль
story not so let’s do that then let’s do it then
расска не так давайте так давайте тогда
no, then let’s look at our
нет Давайте тогда условия смотри наши
conditions: well, the thing is, it’s not
условия такие ну дело в том это не
only ours, it’s
только наши это
uh Ukraine together with NATO Yes, NATO is fighting against
ээ Украина вместе с НАТО Да воюет против
Russia - it’s an alliance of nuclear powers, it
России НАТО - это союз ядерных держав он
can dictate its terms to Russia on the basis of force,
на основе силы может диктовать свои
yes the conditions are like that first,
условия России да условия такие первое
you unconditionally withdraw
вы безоговорочно выводите
uh yours  troops from the territory of Ukraine beyond the
ээ свои войска с территории Украины за
borders of the ninety-first year, so
границы девяносто первого года так
on
дальше
at the Minsk conference
на Минской конференции
reparations will be indicated around wait because
репарации вокруг подожди потому что
Belarus will also be under NATO protectorate
Белорусь будет тоже под протекторатом
then around Ukraine a Tiki
потом вокруг Украины делается Тики
meter-long
метровая
ro canal is dug, filled with water and
ро канал копается заливается водой и
crocodiles are released Yes Kadyrov
пускаются крокодилы Да Кадыров
publicly Putin on Red Square then
публично Путина на Красной площади потом
on  Red Square and Putin and Kadyrov
на Красной площади и Путина и Кадырова
are pulled out of Lenin from the Mausoleum, they are burned
вытягивают Ленина из Мавзолея сжигают
there on this Red Square and they are
их там на этой на Красной площади и
spread across the Kremlin so that it is
наносят по Кремлю чтобы это было так
all so beautiful. And also, by the way, it’s just not easy for you.
красиво всё А ещё Кстати да и тебя
not just, in short, also Kadyrov, not
тебя не просто короче тоже Кадыров не
just, well, Putin, the conditions are impossible, not
просто ну Путин невозможны условия не
Why my conditions Give reasons Why it’s
Почему мои условия Аргументируй Почему
impossible Well, I thought the way was 100% on
невозможно Ну я думал пути зах 100% на
this, it’s not like that, no one will
это не так его же никто не будет
ask him He’ll be tied up, tied up, tied up, tied up,
спрашивать Он связанный
so broken,
связа так в лом
and before that, what should happen  Well, what
а до этого что должно произойти Ну что
should happen Yes, NATO strikes on the
должно произойти Да удары блока НАТО по
territory of the Russian Federation Yes A
территории Российской Федерации Да
palace coup in Russia That is, as
Дворцовый переворот в России То есть как
usual with you You usually
обычно у вас У вас же обычно царя
killed the Tsar with your own truth, either with a snuff box or with a
убивали свои же правда то табакерка то
scarf or something else and so on,
шарфом то ещё что-то травну и так дальше
yes, that is, also do  there will be a Palace
да то есть также сделать будет Дворцовый
coup, your elite wants to
переворот ваша элита она хочет снова
teach children in the West again Yes, she wants to
учить детей на западе Да она хочет
go to normal resorts to relax Yes,
ездить на нормальные курорты отдыхать Да
and they don’t need it in short
и не нужен короче
Putin they will exchange Putin and Kadyrov in one or two in
Путин они на раз-два разменяет Путина и
short for normal relations
Кадырова короче на нормальные отношения
with the West Who are your elite oligarchs
с западом Кто они ваши элиты олигархи
all sorts of Rotenbergs And so  further Do you believe
всякие ротенберги И так дальше Вы верите
in this yes yes yes I will say more Yes
в это да да да я я больше скажу Да
if the option Yes because well you have such
если опцию Да потому что ну ты таких как
interesting geopolitical events but
бы интересных геополитических событий но
Well when will it be I for you what is your name
Ну когда это будет я по тебя как зовут
Denis Denis surname
Денис Денис фамилия
[music]
[музыка]
Which I won’t say okay where are you from St. Petersburg
Какая не скажу ладно откуда ты из Питера
from St. Petersburg, I will ask that they find this
из Питера я попрошу чтобы нашли этого
Denis from St. Petersburg and that Kadyrov,
Дениса из Питера и чтоб Кадыров его
together with Putin, also TET you know
заодно вместе с путином тоже ТЕТ знаешь
how almost the same with you as on
как поч те с тобой тоже самое что и с
the way, I initially asked for a break,
пути я изначально спросил передышке
I just
просто я
see you will have such a
смот у тебя будет такая
backside, then I will ask for a
задка потом я попрошу чтобы сделали
break  while he's Putin you'll stop
передышку пока он будет Путина ты перех
and then he'll come back again and continue you'll
а потом он вернётся снова и продолжит ты
already have a break and he'll
уже у тебя будет передышка и он
continue
продолжит
Norno sulfur I seriously want
Норно серно Я серьёзно нуты хочешь
a break or what if it's okay I agree to
передышку или как не окей согласен на
such conditions then you can
такие условия можно
put a plus if Aro properly
тогда поставьте плюс если Аро нормально
combed himself this is shorter than him
расчесал себя этого этому короче его
prospects are not Well, normal with a respite In
перспективы не Ну норм с передышка Всё
short a respite what a respite to give in
короче передышка какой передышка отдать
short damn Kherson region
короче блин херсонскую область
Zaporizhzhya Donetsk Yes which they
запорожскую донецкую Да который они не
can’t take like yes a
могут взять типа да
respite so that they In short, further
передышка чтобы они Короче дальше
gain a foothold and then go on, subscribe to
закрепились и дальше пошли подпишись на
my Telegram right now he’s a popk
мий Telegram прямо зараз он а попк
tse more and more respectfully YouTube  occupying us
це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня нас
through skarg or in your ban and even more
через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I don’t show people often I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about the stream For this purpose,
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we need Mali to write an operational link
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right away and while there in telegra okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video shchetezh va and korisna information and
видео ще теж ва и корисна информация и
we pon va tma
мы пон ва тма
operational link
оперативный звязок
in this case, show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe L
подпишись L